{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "2x^2 - 2x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n-4x + 3 | -8x^3 + 14x^2 - 26x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 + 14x^2 - 26x + 15) / (-4x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 + 2x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n-3x + 2 | -12x^3 + 2x^2 + 7x - 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-12x^3 + 2x^2 + 7x - 2) / (-3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 + 3x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_____________________\n-2x - 2 | 4x^3 - 2x^2 - 4x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^3 - 2x^2 - 4x + 2) / (-2x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n3x + 4 | 15x^2 + 32x + 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 + 32x + 16) / (3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^2 - x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n-4x - 1 | 12x^3 + 7x^2 + 5x + 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^3 + 7x^2 + 5x + 1) / (-4x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 - x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n3x - 4 | -3x^3 + x^2 + 10x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^3 + x^2 + 10x - 8) / (3x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-5x - 5 | 5x^2 + 10x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(5x^2 + 10x + 5) / (-5x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n5x + 2 | 15x^2 - 14x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 - 14x - 8) / (5x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^2 - 3x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;__________________\n3x - 3 | -15x^3 + 6x^2 + 9\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^3 + 6x^2 + 9) / (3x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 - 3x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n-2x - 5 | -10x^3 - 19x^2 + 17x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^3 - 19x^2 + 17x + 5) / (-2x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n-3x - 5 | 3x^2 - 10x - 25\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^2 - 10x - 25) / (-3x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n-4x - 1 | -4x^2 - 17x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^2 - 17x - 4) / (-4x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\nx + 5 | 5x^2 + 21x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(5x^2 + 21x - 20) / (x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n4x + 1 | -12x^2 - 7x - 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-12x^2 - 7x - 1) / (4x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 - 4x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n-5x - 2 | 20x^3 + 28x^2 + 33x + 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^3 + 28x^2 + 33x + 10) / (-5x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 - x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n2x + 3 | 10x^3 + 13x^2 - x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(10x^3 + 13x^2 - x + 3) / (2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 - 2x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n-3x - 2 | -15x^3 - 4x^2 - 8x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^3 - 4x^2 - 8x - 8) / (-3x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 + 4x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n-4x - 2 | 4x^3 - 14x^2 + 8x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^3 - 14x^2 + 8x + 8) / (-4x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n3x + 5 | -9x^2 - 6x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-9x^2 - 6x + 15) / (3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_____________\n-x + 1 | 2x^2 - x - 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^2 - x - 1) / (-x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 - 2x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n2x + 1 | -4x^3 - 6x^2 - 4x - 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^3 - 6x^2 - 4x - 1) / (2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________\n-x + 3 | x^2 - 8x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(x^2 - 8x + 15) / (-x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\nx - 5 | -3x^2 + 16x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 + 16x - 5) / (x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\nx + 1 | -3x^2 - 2x + 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 - 2x + 1) / (x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\nx + 1 | -4x^2 - 9x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^2 - 9x - 5) / (x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x^2 + 3x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n5x - 3 | 5x^3 + 12x^2 + 11x - 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(5x^3 + 12x^2 + 11x - 12) / (5x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;__________________\n5x + 5 | -10x^2 + 10x + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^2 + 10x + 20) / (5x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n-3x + 1 | -12x^2 - 11x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-12x^2 - 11x + 5) / (-3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n-x - 4 | -3x^2 - 17x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 - 17x - 20) / (-x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 + 2x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\nx + 3 | -2x^3 - 4x^2 + 11x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-2x^3 - 4x^2 + 11x + 15) / (x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 + 3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n2x + 5 | 8x^3 + 26x^2 + 21x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^3 + 26x^2 + 21x + 15) / (2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-3x - 2 | -3x^2 - 5x - 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 - 5x - 2) / (-3x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 + 2x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n-2x - 2 | 2x^3 - 2x^2 - 12x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^3 - 2x^2 - 12x - 8) / (-2x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 - x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n3x + 4 | 12x^3 + 13x^2 - 13x - 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^3 + 13x^2 - 13x - 12) / (3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________\n-x - 2 | 2x^2 + 2x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^2 + 2x - 4) / (-x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n-3x + 5 | 15x^2 - 28x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 - 28x + 5) / (-3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\nx + 5 | -4x^2 - 18x + 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^2 - 18x + 10) / (x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-x + 2 | -3x^2 + 2x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 + 2x + 8) / (-x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 - 4x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n5x + 5 | -5x^3 - 25x^2 - 25x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 - 25x^2 - 25x - 5) / (5x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 + 5x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;___________________\n-4x + 4 | -8x^3 - 12x^2 + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 - 12x^2 + 20) / (-4x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 + x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n3x + 3 | -6x^3 - 3x^2 - 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-6x^3 - 3x^2 - 3) / (3x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n5x + 4 | 20x^2 - 9x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^2 - 9x - 20) / (5x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 + x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n5x + 2 | -20x^3 - 3x^2 + 7x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-20x^3 - 3x^2 + 7x + 2) / (5x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2 - 4x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n-5x - 1 | -15x^3 + 17x^2 + 19x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^3 + 17x^2 + 19x + 3) / (-5x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-2x + 2 | 2x^2 - 10x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^2 - 10x + 8) / (-2x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n-3x + 5 | 15x^2 - 37x + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 - 37x + 20) / (-3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 + 2x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________\n-2x - 1 | 8x^3 + 2x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^3 + 2x + 2) / (-2x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2 + 5x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n-2x + 1 | -6x^3 - 7x^2 - 3x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-6x^3 - 7x^2 - 3x + 4) / (-2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_____________\n-x + 4 | x^2 - 5x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(x^2 - 5x + 4) / (-x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n5x - 5 | -15x^2 + 20x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^2 + 20x - 5) / (5x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\nx - 4 | -2x^2 + 5x + 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-2x^2 + 5x + 12) / (x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^2 + x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\nx - 2 | -3x^3 + 7x^2 - 6x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^3 + 7x^2 - 6x + 8) / (x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-4x + 5 | 8x^2 + 6x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^2 + 6x - 20) / (-4x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;__________________\n5x + 5 | -10x^2 - 25x - 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^2 - 25x - 15) / (5x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 - 3x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n2x - 5 | 4x^3 - 16x^2 + 11x + 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^3 - 16x^2 + 11x + 10) / (2x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_____________\n-x - 2 | x^2 - 2x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(x^2 - 2x - 8) / (-x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 - 3x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n5x - 3 | 10x^3 - 21x^2 - 6x + 9\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(10x^3 - 21x^2 - 6x + 9) / (5x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 - 4x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n4x + 1 | -16x^3 - 20x^2 + 8x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-16x^3 - 20x^2 + 8x + 3) / (4x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\nx + 4 | -3x^2 - 14x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 - 14x - 8) / (x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n3x - 2 | -3x^2 + 5x - 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 + 5x - 2) / (3x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 - 2x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n5x - 4 | 25x^3 - 30x^2 + 28x - 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(25x^3 - 30x^2 + 28x - 16) / (5x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;____________\n-2x - 2 | -10x^2 + 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^2 + 10) / (-2x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 - 4x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n3x - 1 | -6x^3 - 10x^2 - 8x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-6x^3 - 10x^2 - 8x + 4) / (3x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 + 2x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n-x - 4 | 4x^3 + 14x^2 - 3x + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^3 + 14x^2 - 3x + 20) / (-x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^2 + 3x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n-3x + 3 | 9x^3 - 18x^2 - 6x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(9x^3 - 18x^2 - 6x + 15) / (-3x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 - 3x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n-3x - 2 | 3x^3 + 11x^2 + 12x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^3 + 11x^2 + 12x + 4) / (-3x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n-4x - 2 | 12x^2 + 10x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 + 10x + 2) / (-4x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n5x - 1 | 10x^2 + 8x - 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(10x^2 + 8x - 2) / (5x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n4x + 5 | 12x^2 - 5x - 25\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 - 5x - 25) / (4x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-3x + 1 | 6x^2 - 17x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^2 - 17x + 5) / (-3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 + 3x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\nx - 3 | 2x^3 - 3x^2 - 5x - 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^3 - 3x^2 - 5x - 12) / (x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2 + 5x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n5x + 1 | 15x^3 + 28x^2 + 20x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^3 + 28x^2 + 20x + 3) / (5x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 - 3x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n5x - 3 | -5x^3 - 12x^2 + 29x - 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 - 12x^2 + 29x - 12) / (5x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\n-x + 3 | -4x^2 + 8x + 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^2 + 8x + 12) / (-x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n4x - 4 | 12x^2 - 4x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 - 4x - 8) / (4x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n5x - 2 | -5x^2 - 23x + 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^2 - 23x + 10) / (5x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n-4x - 5 | -8x^2 - 22x - 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^2 - 22x - 15) / (-4x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-3x - 1 | -3x^2 + 8x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 + 8x + 3) / (-3x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________\nx + 2 | -4x^2 - 11x - 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^2 - 11x - 6) / (x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-3x - 5 | 3x^2 - 7x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^2 - 7x - 20) / (-3x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-5x - 3 | -5x^2 + 2x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^2 + 2x + 3) / (-5x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 + 3x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n-3x + 1 | 3x^3 - 10x^2 - 12x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^3 - 10x^2 - 12x + 5) / (-3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n-4x + 4 | 12x^2 - 32x + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 - 32x + 20) / (-4x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 - x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n-2x - 2 | -8x^3 - 6x^2 - 2x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 - 6x^2 - 2x - 4) / (-2x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2 - 2x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________________\n2x + 2 | -2x^3 - 6x^2 - 2x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-2x^3 - 6x^2 - 2x + 2) / (2x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-x + 5 | 2x^2 - 8x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^2 - 8x - 10) / (-x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 + 3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\n-5x - 3 | -10x^3 - 21x^2 - 24x - 9\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^3 - 21x^2 - 24x - 9) / (-5x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 + 4x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;__________________________\n5x - 2 | -10x^3 + 24x^2 + 17x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^3 + 24x^2 + 17x - 10) / (5x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 - 2x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________________\nx + 4 | -4x^3 - 18x^2 - 12x - 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^3 - 18x^2 - 12x - 16) / (x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 - 2x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n3x - 2 | 12x^3 - 14x^2 - 2x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^3 - 14x^2 - 2x + 4) / (3x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;___________\n-4x - 4 | 12x^2 - 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 - 12) / (-4x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^2 + 5x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;______________\n-x - 1 | 5x^3 - 6x - 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(5x^3 - 6x - 1) / (-x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 - 2x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n-3x - 5 | 6x^3 + 16x^2 + 16x + 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^3 + 16x^2 + 16x + 10) / (-3x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\nx - 2 | 4x^2 - 11x + 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^2 - 11x + 6) / (x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 - 3x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________________\n-4x - 5 | -8x^3 + 2x^2 + 11x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 + 2x^2 + 11x - 5) / (-4x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_______________\n-2x + 5 | 6x^2 - 7x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^2 - 7x - 20) / (-2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^2 - 4x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;__________________________\n4x - 2 | -12x^3 - 10x^2 + 28x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-12x^3 - 10x^2 + 28x - 10) / (4x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;_________________\n-2x - 5 | 10x^2 + 15x - 25\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(10x^2 + 15x - 25) / (-2x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2 - 4x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;___________________\n-5x - 5 | -15x^3 + 5x^2 - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^3 + 5x^2 - 20) / (-5x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^2 + 3x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;\u0026nbsp;________________________\n-5x + 2 | -15x^3 - 9x^2 - 14x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^3 - 9x^2 - 14x + 8) / (-5x + 2)", "type": "text"}
]}